Hey guys, Pastor Myers here. I want to
invite you to check out this very
powerful message entitled The Devil's
Advocate. And uh it's going to reveal
some very powerful things about the law
of God and the grace and mercy of
Christ. So check it out and be blessed.
[Music]
God commended him as righteous.
By faith, Noah trusted God and
constructed an ark for the deliverance
of his family.
By faith, Abraham was willing to
sacrifice Isaac, his only son, believing
God would still fulfill his promises.
By faith, Moses chose to be mistreated
with the people of God rather than enjoy
sin's fleeting pleasure.
By faith, God's chosen nation crossed
the Red Sea on dry ground and praised
him as it swallowed up the Egyptians.
By faith, Rahab the prostitute escaped
destruction because she welcomed the
spies in peace.
Time will fail me if I tell of Gideon,
David, and the prophets. By faith, they
administered justice. shut the mouths of
lions, quenched raging fire. But others
were imprisoned, murdered, and wandered
in deserts, mountains, and openings in
the earth. We are surrounded by this
great cloud of witnesses.
So get rid of every weight, of every
sin, and run, run with endurance the
race set before us.
Keep your eyes fixed on Jesus. He is the
champion and guide of our faith. For
promised joy, he endured the cross,
thought nothing of its shame, and having
risen again, has been handed his
deserved glory at the right hand of the
throne of God.
[Music]
Title of the sermon once again is the
devil's advocate and it is subtitled
understanding justification by faith and
its counterfeit. And there are many
counterfeits. We're only dealing with
one counterfeit of justification by
faith today. What does it mean to be the
devil's advocate? Let's go to the book
of John 8:41.
Beginning with verse 41, Jesus is
speaking to the Pharisees. And here's
what he says. He says, "You do the deeds
of your father." Then said they to him,
"We be not born of fornication. We have
one father, even God." Jesus said unto
them, "If God were your father,
you would love me. For I proceeded forth
and came from God. Neither came I of
myself, but he sent me. Why do you not
understand my speech? Even because you
cannot hear my word. You are of your
father, the devil, and the lust of your
father you will do. He was a murderer
from the beginning, and abode not in the
truth, because there is no truth in him.
When he speaketh a lie, he speaketh of
his own, for he is a liar
and the father of it. And because I tell
you the truth, you believe me not. Which
of you convinceth me of sin? And if I
say the truth, why do you not believe
me? He that is of God heareth my words,
or heareth God's words. You therefore
hear them not because you are not of
God. Okay,
this is Jesus rebuking the religious
leaders of his day. And what he says to
them is is really quite amazing. He says
you're doing the work of your father.
He's saying you are advocating for your
father. Now you may believe that you are
following God, but you're actually
advocating
for
your father, which he says is the devil.
If it was possible for religious people
to advocate for the devil in Jesus's
day, how much more do you think it is
possible as as the devil has increased
in power as time goes on? As as as
wickedness has increased, how much more
likely do you think it is? How much more
possible do you think it is that that
those in these times who who claim to be
followers of Christ, claim to be
followers of God, are actually
advocating for the devil, being the
devil's advocate.
If it was possible then, it is possible
now. But I want to let you know as harsh
as that sounds and I believe that there
are many
many so-called so-called Christians
people who say I'm a follower of God who
are actually advocating on behalf of the
devil even though there are many there
is good news because the Bible says in
Revelation 3 19 note what the scripture
says as many as I love I rebuke and
chasen be zealous us therefore and
repent. Now, who does God love?
John 3:16 tells us that God so loved the
world. Amen. So, if God loves the world,
and if the world is wicked, uh we know
that that if God loves the world, that
would include even well-meaning
Christians
who are also
advocating for the enemy without
realizing that they're doing it. And why
is this good news? Because God still
offers mercy
to those who know not what they do. Are
y'all with me so far? So if you're
watching this and and you know you may
not uh uh have all understanding of the
Bible, you may learn today, whoa, I have
been a an advocate for the enemy. I
didn't even know it. If you are learning
that today about yourself, guess what?
God
is not casting you off. He has brought
you here to hear this message today.
Because he loves you. Because he loves
you.
Right? No. Not Notice with me. Notice
with me. Acts 17:30. The Bible says, "At
the times of this ignorance, God wked
at, but
now commandeth all men everywhere to
repent." You see to it it for us to set
the foundation rightly. You need to
understand that
God winks at ignorance. If you don't
know better,
God is winking at that. But when he
brings light, he expects you to respond.
Amen. That's a fair God. That's a loving
God. That's a just God. You see the
scales on either side of me. the scales
of justice, right? God is a God that is
just.
And so if God is a God that is just, we
want to make sure that we are in no way
advocating for the devil.
The question for us today is, is it
possible in ignorance to actually be the
devil's advocate?
The first thing that we need to do,
beloved, is to to to to
no longer be ignorant.
If I if I want to make sure that I am
not advocating
for the devil, then I need to know what
does the devil advocate?
What does he advocate? If I know what he
advocates, then I will know stay away
from that thing. Why? cuz I don't want
to be what everyone the devil's
advocate.
So what we're going to do today beloved
is we're going to look at several things
that the devil is advocating and see if
you are advocating for these things too.
You are the devil's advocate.
But again,
praise God, you're not the devil.
You're just ignorantly being his
advocate. And guess what? God offers
mercy to all of those who at one time
advocated the devil's lies,
advocated the devil's errors. So come
on, what is the devil advocating? Well,
we can get a few clues just by looking
at scripture. Let's go to 2
Thessalonians chapter 2:3.
2 Thessalonians chapter 2:3. And I want
you to notice what the ESV version of
the Bible says regarding this verse. It
says, "Let no one deceive you in any
way, for that day will not come, that
day meaning the second coming of Christ,
unless the rebellion comes first and the
man of lawlessness is revealed, the son
of destruction."
Here's what the KJV version says.
Let no man deceive you by any means, for
that day shall not come except there
come a falling away first and the man of
sin be revealed, the son of predition.
So what I want you to know, beloved, is
that in the ESV, it's the man of
lawlessness. In the KJV, it's the man of
sin. And what I'm simply showing you
here, beloved, is that Satan, what we
can know from this verse is that Satan
advocates
lawlessness. Put that word in the chat
for me, please. Lawlessness. Satan
advocates for lawlessness. Therefore, I
know that if I am advocating
lawlessness, I am in essence advocating
for the devil.
So the question now becomes what is
lawlessness? What is sin? And again note
what the Bible tells us in first John
chapter 3 and verse4. Whosoever
committeth sin transgresses also the law
for sin is the transgression of the law.
Sin is the transgression of the law. So
again we are clearly seeing here laid
out that if I am advocating lawlessness
or sin which is transgression of the
law. I am actually advocating
for the devil.
I am actually being his advocate.
But I need you to understand this a
little bit deeper. Right? We got to go a
little bit deeper because there are many
Christians who will say, "Oh, no. You
know, I think everything ought to be
good, but let's hold on and slow down
for a moment." Note with me what the
Bible says about Lucifer in heaven. In
Ezekiel 28:1 15, the Bible says of
Lucifer, "Thou was perfect in thy ways
from the day that thou was created till
iniquity was found in thee." That's the
same word for lawlessness. It's the same
word for sin. So we see that Lucifer,
the devil, Satan, was an advocate of
iniquity, an advocate of lawlessness.
Now, while he was advocating lawlessness
in heaven, note what else the Bible says
about him in Isaiah 14:12. The Bible
says here, "How art thou fallen from
heaven, oh Lucifer, son of the morning?
How art thou cut down to the ground
which did weaken the nations? For thou
hast said in thine heart, I will ascend
into heaven. I will exalt my throne
above the stars of God. I will sit also
upon the mount of the congregation in
the size of the north.
I will ascend above the heights of the
clouds. I will be like the most high.
Come back with me for a moment.
Isaiah chapter 14 lets us know that
Lucifer claimed that he could be like
God. Not only like God in power but like
God in holiness because God is holiness.
So Lucifer was in essence saying I can
be holy like God and I don't need a law
telling me how to do it. This is how he
deceived onethird of the angels. He did
not deceive a third of the angels by
inviting them to be evil. He was
promoting a principle. He was listen to
me.
He was advocating something. And the
thing he was advocating was I can
determine for myself
what is right and what is wrong.
I can determine and decide for myself
what is right, what is wrong, and I
don't need a law to do it. Now, please
note, at the same time, the Bible speaks
of the angels
in heaven who did keep God's
commandments. Notice what the Bible
says. Psalm 103:20, "Bless the Lord, ye
his angels,
that excel in strength, that do his
commandments, hearkening unto the voice
of his word." So clearly we see here
that there were angels in heaven that
did God's commandments, that do God's
commandments, and there were angels in
heaven, Lucifer included, that came to
the conclusion that they did not need to
keep God's law.
Are y'all with me so far?
So then, so then what Lucifer was was
advocating
was this idea of I can be holy
without a law. I don't need anybody,
including God's law, telling me what is
right and what is wrong. Notice with me
something else that Lucifer was
advocating. Ezekiel 28:16, the Bible
says, "By the multitude of thy
merchandise, they have filled the midst
of thee with violence," speaking of
Lucifer, "and thou hast sinned.
Therefore, I will cast thee as profane
out of the mountain of God." Now, note,
let me read it again. By the multitude
of thy merchandise, they have filled the
midst of thee with violence. Now, what
does that mean, filled the midst of thee
with violence? This word filled, the the
Hebrew word fulfilled here, it means
simply to be full of,
to accomplish,
to confirm,
to consecrate, to to be at an end, to be
expired, uh to be fenced, to be filled,
to fulfill, to flow, fullness, furnish,
gather. Okay.
So basically
the word describes being filled up.
Lucifer was filled up. Now why is this
significant to understand? Well, because
the same word is used in Genesis 6:1
when the Bible says the earth was also
corrupt before God and the earth was
filled with violence.
We know that when the earth became
filled with violence that they had
crossed a line of no return. In essence
then we know that Lucifer eventually
crossed a line of no return.
His cup Clint iniquity was filled. The
cup was filled meaning there was no
turning back. There was no there was no
point of return for Lucifer. Now why is
this significant? Because
in the book of Matthew chapter 18, Jesus
lays out a principle which we must
understand in the context that Christ is
the same yesterday, today, and forever.
He changes not. He operates the same way
regardless of who you are. And notice
what it says in Matthew 18 verse 21. The
Bible says here, "Then came Peter to him
and said,"Lord, how often shall my
brother sin against me, and I forgive
him till seven times?" Jesus saith unto
him, "I say not unto thee until seven
times, but until 70*
7." Okay, so let's let's come back for a
moment.
It is Jesus's mode of operation to offer
forgiveness, to offer mercy. That's who
he is. That is who God is. Therefore, we
can know
that mercy had been extended to Lucifer.
However,
we can also know that Lucifer rejected
that mercy.
Are y'all with me so far?
You see, in order to obtain mercy, it
would have required Lucifer to repent.
So, please put a one in the chat. You
need to get this point very clearly. In
order for Lucifer to get mercy, it would
have required a spirit of repentance.
Man, I really messed up.
Lord, I'm sorry. We don't know how that
would have played out.
But here's what we do know.
Lucifer never repented.
Okay? So, you don't want to repent.
You're not going to you're not going to
repent from your sin or in other words,
repent from your lawlessness.
Okay.
Well, if you're not going to repent from
your lawlessness,
then you have to leave heaven.
And what happens when God says to
Lucifer, "You have to leave heaven."
Well, let me show you what happens. If
we go to Isaiah chapter 14, where the
Bible says, "For thou has said in thine
heart, I will ascend into heaven. I will
exalt my throne above the stars of God.
I will sit also upon the mount of the
congregation in the size of the north."
What I want you to understand here is
that Lucifer wanted heaven. He wanted
heaven,
but he was not willing to repent.
He was not willing to repent from his
lawlessness.
But he wanted heaven. And he wanted
heaven so bad that that in Revelation
chapter 4 or chapter 12, the Bible says
verse 7, the Bible says that there was
war in heaven. Michael and his angels
fought against the dragon and the dragon
fought and his angels. So then please
follow this. Number one,
Lucifer was advocating that he could be
holy without God's law.
And number two, he was advocating,
I will not repent, but should have
access to heaven anyway.
All right, Joe,
let me repeat that. Lucifer was
advocating, I can be holy without a law
telling me how to be holy. And number
two, I I am not going to repent,
but I deserve heaven anyway. I should
get into heaven any I should have
heaven. He was already in heaven. I
should have heaven even though I'm
unwilling to repent. All right, are
y'all following me? Do y'all catch this?
Therefore, therefore,
Lucifer's
principle,
what Lucifer
pushes is the idea that holiness is
possible,
determining it for yourself. You don't
need a law telling you what holiness is.
And number two, he will advocate the
principle that repentance
for breaking the law is not necessary.
and you should still have access to
heaven. Okay, so let's lay that to the
side for a moment. And now I want you to
we're going to go on another journey,
but just follow along carefully. So
let's let's let's let's just put that to
the side for a second. And now we're
going to go to the book of Genesis.
And in the book of Genesis, we have the
creation account where God creates the
earth in six days and he rests on the
seventh. Um, in that creation account,
there is something missing. There is no
discussion of the creation of angels.
What does this tell us? The 7-day
creation did not include
God's creation of angels. Angels were
created way before the creation of the
earth.
And you have to understand that in order
to understand how earth gets involved in
this conflict that originated way before
earth began and originated in heaven.
So so this rebellion Lucifer's rebellion
began before the creation of man. A and
when we understand that we can now
understand a very a peculiar verse in
Ezekiel chapter 28:1 17. Notice what the
Bible says here. Ezekiel 28:17, "Thine
heart was lifted up because of thy
beauty," speaking of Lucifer. "Thou has
corrupted thy wisdom by reason of thy
brightness. I will cast thee to the
ground. I will lay thee before kings
that they may behold thee." God is
telling Lucifer that I'm going to lay
you before a group of kings. We don't
know who those are. Who are the who is
this group of kings that God was going
to lay before Lucifer
to be judged?
to be condemned?
Well, we find the answer when we look at
a principle God laid out for the
children of Israel in the Old Testament.
Notice with me Deuteronomy 19:16, the
Bible says, "If a false witness rise up
against any man to testify against him
that which is wrong, then both the men
between whom the controversy is shall
stand before the Lord, before the
priests and the judges, which shall be
in those days.
And the judges shall make diligent
inquisition. And behold, if the witness
be a false witness, and has testified
falsely against his brother, then shall
you do unto him, as he had thought to
have done unto his brother, so shalt
thou put away the evil from among you.
So what we see here is God lays out a
principle that whenever a controversy
rises between two people or two parties,
there must be a third neutral party, a
jury that would be responsible for
judging between the two.
When you understand this, you will also
come to understand the amazing
conclusion that when Paul writes in 1
Corinthians chapter 6:2, speaking of the
redeemed saints, when Paul writes these
words, "Do you not know that the saints
shall judge the world? And if the world
shall be judged by you, are you unworthy
to judge the smallest matters? Know you
not that we the saints shall judge
angels?
All right.
One of the reasons that God created man,
one of the reasons man was created was
that they were to serve as the jury, as
the judges that would ultimately condemn
the devil and his angels.
Are y'all with me so far?
That's why, beloved, if we are the jury,
then
how crazy would it be
that people on the jury
are being the devil's advocate?
Do I need to say that again?
If we are the jury, if God has called
mankind to be the jury,
then how crazy would it be if the devil
could get the jury to actually become
the devil's
advocates
by promoting his principles that he was
pushing in heaven. How insane would that
be? How ingenious would that be for
Satan to lead the very jurors, the very
ones who claim to follow Christ to push
for his theories.
All right, come on. Let let let's check
this out. Come with me to the book of
Romans, chapter 13. Romans chapter 13.
The Bible says, "Owe no man anything but
to love one another. For he that loveth
one another has fulfilled the law. For
this sh thou shalt not kill, thou commit
adultery. Thou shalt not kill. Thou
shalt not steal. Thou shalt not bear
false witness. Thou shalt not covet. And
if there be any other commandment, it is
briefly comprehended in this saying,
namely, thou shalt love thy neighbor as
thyself. Verse 10, love workketh no ill
to his neighbor. Therefore, love is the
fulfilling of the law. In heaven,
beloved, the law was very simply known
as love.
That's what the law was in heaven. You
say there was a law in heaven. Yes, that
law was the law of love. It was just a
simple word, love. Now, why is this
significant? Because in 1 John 4:8 and
verse 16, the Bible says God is love.
So, hold on. Watch this. If the law, if
the fulfilling of the law is love and
God is love, oh man, do y'all understand
this? If the law is love and God is
love, your attack upon the law is an
attack upon God.
Should I say that again?
If the law is love and God is love, then
the law is a is the very reflection of
who God is.
So when Lucifer attacked the law in
heaven, he was attacking God.
He was attacking love.
This very same law of love was written
on the hearts of Adam and Eve. How do we
know that? Because the Bible says in
Romans chapter 2:14, "For when the
Gentiles," this talking about the
Gentiles, y'all, not talking about Adam
and Eve, talking about the Gentiles.
For when the Gentiles, which have not
the law, do by nature the things
contained in the law, these having not
the law, are a law unto themselves,
which show the work of the law written
in their hearts. Stop right there. If
sinful Gentiles thousands of years after
the creation of Adam and Eve have
remnants of the law of God written on
their hearts, do you not think that when
Adam and Eve were created, God had
written the law on their hearts?
Absolutely. It was the law of love.
That's the law that was written on their
hearts. Are y'all with me so far?
And then the Bible says this in Genesis
2:1. Thus the heavens and the earth were
finished, and all the host of them. And
on the seventh day, God ended his work
which he had made. And he rested on the
seventh day from all his work which he
had made. And God blessed the seventh
day and sanctified it because in it he
had rested from all the work all the his
work which God created and made. God
gave man the Sabbath as a sign or symbol
that the earth was good.
That the earth was was was
in harmony
with the state of heaven.
Are y'all with me so far? The reason God
gave man the Sabbath, in fact, notice
with me Mark chapter 27.
The Bible is Jesus speaking here. Jesus
said unto them, "The Sabbath was made
for man." Just stop right there. Just
stop right there. You can read and not
man for the Sabbath. When God created
the world, he didn't make the Sabbath
and then made man to No, no, no, no. He
made man and then made the Sabbath as a
gift to the earth.
this gift.
When you make something for someone,
it's a gift. If someone gives you a
gift, you keep the gift. You treasure
the gift. And this gift was a sign that
heaven and earth were in harmony. They
were on the same page.
Heaven is good. Earth is good. The only
way this sign could be broken is if Adam
and Eve gave dominion over to Satan. If
they listened to the enemy, then the
state of rest on earth, the state of
peace on earth would be broken.
So
we know that sin was a transgression of
the law. When Adam and Eve sinned, they
transgressed the law of love. Now watch
this. After they transgressed the law of
love, you know what Satan's next step
was? His next step was to lead them to
the after they ate from the tree of the
knowledge of good and evil, which would
bring death because of their
disobedience,
Satan wanted to lead them to the tree of
life.
so that they could eat and live forever
as transgressors of the law. Hey, watch
the principle. I can eat, I can disobey
and still live forever. I can disobey
and still have access to the tree of
life. This is what Satan was advocating.
I can disregard the law of God and I
should still have the right to eat from
the tree of life. I should still have
the right
to access the things of God.
So, Genesis chapter 3 tells us, the
Bible says, "And the Lord God said,
behold, the man has become as one of us
to know good and evil, lest he put forth
his hand and also take also of the tree
of life and eat and live forever.
Therefore, the Lord God sent him forth
from the garden of Eden to till the
ground from whence he was taken." So he
drove out the man and placed at the east
of the garden of Eden cherubams and a
flaming sword which turned every way to
keep the way of the tree of life. All
right. So what we see here is the entire
plan of salvation unfolding before us.
What we see here is is is Satan's
principle, what Satan was advocating
unfolding before us. You don't have to
obey God. Adam and Eve, you can be like
God without obeying him. You don't need
to obey his law. You can be like him.
And then once you're like him, once
you've disobeyed, you can still live
forever. You can still have access to
the things of God. You can still eat of
the tree of life. We know that these two
principles are principles advocated by
the devil. If we find ourselves
advocating those principles, therefore,
we are being the devil's advocate. And I
will show you how. I will show you how.
But the first thing I want you to see,
beloved, is is we are about to watch the
process of redemption unfold right
before our eyes. Because in Genesis
chapter 3:7,
what I'm what I'm about to show you
is that the very first thing that we
must do
to receive the grace, the mercy, to
receive the to receive the the the
salvation that God has laid out for us
is what? Can y'all put it in the chat?
What is the very first thing that must
happen?
We must
repent.
Very simple, y'all. Repent.
The thing that Satan said, "I'm not
doing" is the thing that we must do.
Repent. Let me show you. In Genesis 3:7,
the Bible says here, Genesis 3:7, uh,
"And the eyes of them both were open,
and they knew that they were naked, and
they sewed fig leaves together, and made
themselves aprons. And they heard the
voice of the Lord God walking in the
garden in the cool of the day. And Adam
and his wife hid themselves from the
presence of the Lord God amongst the
trees of the garden." And the Lord God
called unto Adam, and said unto him,
"Where art thou?" And he said, "I heard
thy voice in the garden and I was afraid
because I was naked and I hid myself." I
was afraid.
I was afraid.
Now, now when you've read this verse
before, you said to yourself, "Oh, they
were terrified and they ran away. They
were afraid." However, however, this
word afraid, it literally means, let's
go to the screen. It literally means to
fear. Now, watch this. morally to revere
causitatively to frighten to be
afrighted afraid dreadful to put in fear
to be had in reverence hold on a minute
wait a minute Psalm 86:1 says teach me
thy way oh Lord I will walk in thy truth
unite my heart to fear thy name may I
suggest to you that the reason that Adam
and Eve
hid themselves from God is because they
reverenced him enough to know we messed
up. We did something wrong. We are
ashamed. We are sorrowful for what we've
done. What do y'all think?
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. They were afraid.
But they were afraid because they
understood the holiness of God. They
reverenced God. They realized they had
done something wrong. And beloved, that
in that reverence was their repentance.
They weren't bold like, "Yeah, God,
what? We did it." They were afraid. They
were They were like, "We messed up." And
the fact that they acknowledged that
they messed up. Acknowledged that they
had done wrong. Then God comes to them
in the garden. And watch what the Bible
says. Unto Adam also, and to his wife
did the Lord God make coats of skin and
clothe them. Do y'all see this? This is
beautiful, y'all.
Here you have the entire process of
salvation laid out. We admit
that we have done wrong. We're not going
to hide anything. We're not going to We
We have done wrong. God comes to them.
What'd you do? She made me do it. Says
to Eve, "What'd you do?" the devil made
me do it. But they acknowledge their
wrong.
They they are repentant.
And what does God do? He says, "All
right, I'm going to cover you. I'm going
to a an animal is going to be sacrificed
and that animal skin is going to cover
you. There you have the entire plan of
salvation. I am sorry for what I've
done. If I have the chance to eat from
the tree again, I would never do it
again." But God says, "But we're just
going to put that sword around the tree
of life." So watch this then. In their
repentance, in their acknowledgment that
yes, we have done wrong, God says, I
grant you mercy. You see how easy that
is? But the devil doesn't want it that.
He's going to try to do everything to
make you not think that you need to
repent.
See, in the very next chapter, we're
about to be introduced to two
worshippers
which parallel the principles of
justification by faith versus
justification of sin. All right, so
let's say that again. Put that in the
chat for me just so that I'll make sure
you got it. In the very next chapter,
we're about to be introduced to a man
named Abel and his brother whose name is
Cain. These are two different
worshippers. They are both worshiping
God, but one represents justification by
faith, meaning I acknowledge that I have
done wrong and I acknowledge that the
wages of sin is death and I will bring
God what he asked for, what he
demonstrated back in the garden. That's
Abel. But Cain says, "Nah, I'm gonna
justify sin.
I'm gonna determine for myself what I
will bring God. At least I'm bringing
him something." He ought to be thankful.
So, so Cain substitutes
for his worship. He substitutes
something that God has not asked for.
And he says, "Here's what I'm going to
give you, and you should be satisfied
with that because I determined that this
is feasible for me."
Justification by faith versus
justification of sin.
And when you justify sin, beloved,
you're being an advocate of the devil.
You are serving as the devil's advocate.
This is what's happening.
So
once again,
how do you tell if you are worshiping
while being the devil's advocate? And
there are three things I want you to
understand here. Three things, three
ways to know that you are worshiping,
you're you're that while you're
worshiping God, you're actually being
the devil's advocate. And that is if I
advocate the things the devil advocates.
So again, we're going to break this
down, but in more detail. Number one,
remember the devil advocates that he
didn't need a law to be holy like God
and therefore will not keep it.
See, the Bible says in 1 John 2:3,
"Hereby we do know that we know him,
that is God, if we keep his
commandments. He that saith, I know God,
and keepeth not his commandments, is an
advocate for the devil.
Do y'all catch this?
Lucifer was against the law of God in
heaven. And now Jesus himself, writing,
speaking to his apostles, says, "He that
sayth, I know him and keepeth not his
commandments is a liar, and the truth is
not in him. Verse five, but who so
keepeth his word in him verily is the
love of God perfected. Hereby know we
that we are in him. See that if I am
advocating if I am saying that I don't
need to keep God's commandments then I
am then let me stop saying I am then you
are advocating the devil's lie.
You are being the devil's advocate by
arguing that we don't have to keep God's
law. You are arguing the very same thing
Lucifer argued in heaven. And this is
why John 8:44 says, "You are of your
father, the devil." Jesus speaking, "The
lust of your fathers will you do." He
was a murderer from the beginning and
abode not in the truth because there is
no truth in him. When he speak of the
lie, he speaks of speakth of his own.
for he is a liar and the father of it.
Now watch this y'all. Check this out.
When
Christians say that the Ten Commandments
is no longer necessary to be kept, you
are getting rid of the law that that
condemns Lucifer as a liar and a
murderer.
Let me say that again. You are literally
advocating for the devil. You're saying,
"Wait a minute.
If if the Ten Commandments no longer
exist, then why should Lucifer still be
punished for being a liar and a
murderer?
If the law no longer exists,
then Lucifer himself should be free from
condemnation. Because Lucifer is in
trouble. Why? Because he's lying. He's
stealing. He's killing. He's murder.
Come on. Y'all know the marijuana laws,
right? Marijuana illegal. 5 years ago,
10 years ago, people in jail for selling
marijuana. And now the government says,
"Hey, marijuana is no longer that law is
done away with. Marijuana in certain
places no longer legal." So what
happens? What happens to those people
who were in jail for selling marijuana?
Oh, now we got to let them go. Now we
got to, you know, commute their
sentences because it's no longer
breaking the law. So if the law of God,
beloved, if the Ten Commandments is done
away with, you are literally
advocating
to set Satan free.
Come on, I'm not making this up. Romans
3:1 19. Now we know that whatsoever
things the law saveth, it's safe to them
that are under the law, that every mouth
may be stopped, and all the world become
guilty before God.
The whole world is guilty before God
because the law condemns them as being
guilty. Thou shalt not lie. Thou shalt
not steal. Thou shalt not commit
adultery. Thou shalt not covet. Thou
shalt not take uh um dishonor mother and
father. All of these things declare the
world as guilty. But the Christian who
says, "Hey, that law was done away with
at the cross, what you're saying is the
whole world should now go free.
The whole world shall not, including
Satan himself. Why, beloved? Because,
check this out. In Romans 4:15, the
Bible says, "Because the law workketh
wrath. Where there is no law, there is
no transgression." So, if the law is
done away with, then Satan isn't guilty
of anything.
If the law is done away with, then the
world is no longer guilty of anything.
And you can't say, "Oh, well, the law
doesn't stand for me, but it stands for
other people." No. Either the law is
done away with or it's not. If it's done
away with, then Satan himself has access
to heaven. And guess what Satan's
pointing to to prove his point? Look at
the Christians.
God.
They are arguing.
They are arguing my very point.
You should let me back into heaven.
Huh?
You see, beloved, in in you wanting to
get into heaven without keeping the law,
you're you're paving the way for Satan's
argument toward God. I should get back
into heaven. I don't keep the law, but I
should if you letting them in.
Now, Satan knows that's not that's not
the way it goes. And God knows that's
that that's not the way it goes.
But his own people
advocating for Satan's argument is for
Satan's principle. Is Satan saying, "I'm
telling you, universe, I'm telling you,
I am right and God is wrong." Even his
own people are advocating my cause.
The Bible says in Romans 14:15, we just
read it, "The law workketh wrath.
Well, why is that significant? Because
in Revelation 14:19 14:9,
the Bible says, "And the third angel
followed them, saying with a loud voice,
if any man worship the beast and his
image, and receive his mark in his
forehead, in his hand, the same shall
drink of the wine of the wrath of God."
Stop. If the law workketh wrath,
and at the end of time those who receive
the mark of the beast receive the wrath
of God, is it not because the wrath of
God is poured out on those who broke the
law,
those who disregarded the law?
What do you think?
We don't have to guess. All we need to
do is look at the very next verse.
That was verse 10. Look at verse 12.
Verse 12 says, "Here is the patience of
the saints. Here are they that keep the
commandments of God and have the have
the faith of Jesus." So those who
receive the mark, whatever that is,
receive the wrath of God. Meaning the
mark has something to do with breaking
the law of God. And then the very next
verse, here's the patience of the
saints. Here are they that keep the
commandments of God.
Do y'all see this? That's one. Number
two. Number two, the argument that the
cross abolished the commandments of God
is advocating the devil's li. You're
advocating on behalf of the devil. Let
me break it down for you very quickly.
This argument, let's go to this to the
slide. This argument that the cross
abolish the ten commandments is a lie
from the devil. It is merchandise from
the devil that many Christians have
bought. Let me break this down for you.
Ignorantly bought, may I add? The Bible
says God is love. Romans 13:10, we just
read it. Love workketh no ill to his
neighbor. But therefore, love is the
fulfilling of the law. If God is love
and and the law is love,
when the law was broken, love was
broken.
Let let me re let me rephrase that. When
the law was broken, love was broken.
Now, the only way that the law could be
fulfilled would be through love. Only
love could fulfill the broken law of
love.
Yeah. Yeah. Did y'all catch that?
So, so if love is the fulfilling of the
law, it's because when you break the
law, you're breaking love. When Cain
killed Abel, that was an act
of lovelessness.
Every act of breaking the law, any of
the commandments, is an act of breaking
love. Breaking love for God, first four
commandments. Breaking love for
neighbor, last six commandments. So
only by love could the law be fulfilled.
Did y'all catch that? Only by love could
the law of love be fulfilled. Hey, love
is broken. How do we fix it? Glue? No.
Um,
uh, let's see. Uh, do we need a saw? No.
There's only one thing that can fulfill
or fill back or fix the broken law, and
that is love.
Now, watch this. According to John
15:13,
the Bible says, "Greater love has no man
than this, than a man laid down his life
for his friends." So in other words, for
this law of love which was equal to God
himself, for that law to be fixed,
not done away with, fixed, restored.
It had to be done through an act of love
equal to God himself,
equal to the law itself.
Now I need y'all to understand something
here because see
this is why an angel could not die for
mankind
because the law existed before angels.
Since the law is an expression of the
person of God, every angel created after
God, every angel God created, none of if
God said to an angel, "Go and die for
them." You know what? You know what that
would prove? God is not love. Cuz you're
sending a lesser being to go die for
someone else.
That's why even some people struggle to
understand, well, God sent his son, you
know, why didn't God come himself? God
did come himself.
The Bible says again, "Greater love has
no man than this, that a man laid down
his life for his friends."
God laid down his life. This, beloved,
demonstrates that Jesus was not brought
forth in in eternity sometime in the
past. If as long as God exists, the law
existed. And as long as the law existed,
God the law and God are equal. Meaning
the one who had to die for that broken
law had to be equal with the law.
Jesus did not come sometime later after
the father. Because if he did, if Jesus
is in any sense in his pre-incarnate
state lesser than God, then God is not
love. because God sent someone less than
himself to do something that required
the greatest act possible.
So then what this demonstrates, beloved,
is that the cross of Calvary magnifies,
demonstrates the holiness of God's law.
It does not get rid of it. It fills it
up.
It demonstrates this is what love is.
So when Christians turn around and
argue, "Yeah, the cross, man, it got rid
of the law." Again, if there is no law,
then Satan has every right to get back
into heaven.
And those who argue that the law of God
is no longer relevant and needed are in
fact arguing for Satan's return to the
kingdom of God. And
and every wicked person who has ever
been condemned and died, they are
arguing what Satan's arguing. We all
should be back in heaven.
The third way to advocate for the devil,
I will not repent, but I should still
have heaven. I will not repent, but I
should still have heaven. We're almost
done, y'all. We're almost done. We're
going to cover this third of the way,
then we're going to wrap this up. I will
not repent, but I still should have
heaven. You see in Ezekiel 18 and:30 the
Bible says therefore I will judge you oh
house of Israel everyone according to
his ways say the Lord God and then he
says this repent and turn yourselves
from all your all all your
transgressions so iniquity shall not be
your ruin. What is repentance?
Repentance is turning away from your
transgression.
Transgression of what?
of the law.
True repentance
is admitting that you were wrong in
something
and it is turning away from that
repeatedly wrong act.
The Bible says in Psalm 51, "Have mercy
upon me, oh God, according to thy loving
kindness, according to unto the
multitude of thy tender mercies. Blot
out my transgressions, wash me from my
iniquity, and cleanse me from my sin.
For I acknowledge my transgressions, and
my sin is ever before me. Isaiah 1:16,
"Wash yourselves, make you clean. Remove
the evil of your deeds from before my
eyes. Cease
to do evil. Cease to transgress from the
law." Repentance is turning away from
lawbreaking.
Did y'all catch it just now? Repentance
is turning away from the act of
continually breaking God's law. This is
why James 2:10 tells us, "For whosoever
shall keep the whole law, and yet offend
in one point, he is guilty of all. For
he that said, do not commit adultery,
one of the ten commandments, said also,
do not kill, one of the ten
commandments." Now, if thou commit no
adultery, yet if thou kill, thou become
a transgressor of the law.
What God is telling us here is if you're
guilty of breaking any of the ten
commandments, you're guilty of breaking
all of them.
And if you're guilty of breaking all of
them, you need to repent for breaking
all of them.
But if the devil could somehow get us to
think that some of these commandments
don't need repenting from
are not that important, no longer stand.
Therefore, I don't need to, nor am I
going to ever repent for breaking this
commandment,
but I should still have heaven.
You understand? When you do this,
you're advocating the very same thing
that Satan advocated. Satan refused to
repent in heaven. What wrong? Hadn't
done anything wrong. What wrong?
Daniel 7:25. Daniel 7:25 tells us
exactly Satan, what Satan would seek to
do. He shall speak great words against
the most high. shall wear out the saints
of the most high and think to change
times and laws. So, if we know from
Daniel 7:25 that the devil's forces that
the devil's pe the devil's uh uh plan is
to change God's law. If we advocate that
same thing and say yes, God's law has
been changed. God's law has been done
away with. God's law no longer stands.
If if we do that, beloved, we are in
fact advocating on behalf of the devil.
Because in order to acknowledge that
you've broken the law, you have to also
acknowledge that the law is holy and
good. That the law still stands. Romans
7:12 says, "Wherefore the law is holy
and the commandment holy and just and
good. Was then that which is good made
death unto me? God forbid, but sin that
it might appear sin. In other words,
Paul says, the purpose of the
commandments is to show me my sinfulness
so that I can repent of all that sin and
then not be saved by my works, but be
covered by the righteousness of Christ.
But it it is all dependent upon my
willingness to admit that I have broken
the law. Admit that I have broken the
Sabbath. Admit that I have broken the
commandment that says, "Thou shalt not
have any graven images, or thou shalt
not lie, or thou shalt not steal." But
if there's any one of these laws that
I'm just like, "Yeah, I don't have to
admit to that one,
but I still want heaven." Guess what?
The repentance is not complete. You say,
"Pastor, what about the millions of
people who are Christians who who didn't
know about that commandment?" If they
didn't know, God winks in their
ignorance. They will be in heaven.
Praise God. Because God is a just and
merciful God. But there are many
Christians today who are teaching that
the law of God no longer stands. Which
means you're in essence saying Lucifer
should have every right to get back into
heaven. Not only are they teaching this,
but what they really are trying to teach
and really are trying to say is that the
Sabbath is no longer binding on
Christians and will use all kinds of
verses in the scriptures taken out of
context to argue the devil's point.
What? That the law of God was changed.
That the law of God was abolished.
I'm not talking about the ceremonial
law. That's why we don't sacrifice
animals anymore or give offerings, meat
offerings and drink offerings. We're
talking about the Sabbath. Now, I see
this this is how good God is. He puts
two prophecies in the Bible, one in the
Old Testament and one in the New to show
no matter what anyone tells you, just
know that I have not changed these laws.
My disciples have not changed these
laws. No matter what you how the
scripture is misinterpreted, know that
if the law is an expression of me and I
change not. If I change not, the law
changes not. Why? Because God is love
and love is a fulfilling of the law. And
if God is the same yesterday, today, and
forever and changes not, then the law is
the same yesterday and today forever and
change is not. To change the law is to
change God.
And if God changes, then God is not
perfect. And if God is not perfect, then
Lucifer's argument is right. Hey, I
should be God. I should sit on the
throne of the most high. I should be
worshiped as God. I will be like the
most high but better.
Isaiah 56. We are almost done. Isaiah
56. Notice the Old Testament prophecy
pointing to Gentiles keeping the Sabbath
under the new covenant. The Bible says,
"Thus sayith the Lord, keep ye judgment
and do justice, for my salvation is near
to come, and my righteousness to be
revealed. Blessed is the man that doeth,
and the Son of man that layeth hold on
it, that keepeth the Sabbath from
polluting it, and keepeth his hand from
doing any evil. Neither let the son of
the stranger, that's the Gentile,
that has joined himself to the Lord,
speak, saying, "The Lord has utterly
separated me from his people." Neither
let the unic say, Behold, I'm a dry
tree. For thus sayith the Lord unto the
unic that keepeth my Sabbath, and choose
the things that please me, and take hold
of my covenant.
The only covenant open to Gentiles,
beloved, is the new covenant. It goes on
to say,
even unto them will I give in my house
and within my walls a place and a name
better than of sons and of daughters. I
will give them an everlasting name that
shall not be cut off. Also the sons of
the strangers, Gentiles that join
themselves to the Lord to serve him and
to love the name of the Lord, to be his
servants, everyone that keepeth the
Sabbath from polluting it, and taketh
hold of my covenant.
Even them will I bring to my holy
mountain, and make them joyful in my
house of prayer. their burnt offerings
and their sacrifices will be accepted on
mine altar. For my house shall be called
a house of prayer for all people. That
means all people are supposed to be
keeping the Sabbath. All people, but the
devil lies. And many Christians are
advocating for the devil. Oh yeah, it's
not for all people. It's just for the
Jews back in the Old Testament.
Come on. How about the New Testament?
God put a prophecy in the New Testament,
too. Just in case anyone tried to pull
the wool over your eyes and tell you
that, oh, the commandments, the Sabbath
is done away with. Jesus himself in
Matthew 24 20-22 says this, "But pray
that your flight be not in the winter,
neither on the Sabbath day. For then,
well, when is then? When is then? For
then shall be great tribulation, such as
was not since the beginning of the world
to this time no nor ever shall be. And
except those days be shortened, there
should no flesh be saved. But for the
elect's sake, those days shall be
shortened. What days? Watch in the very
next verse,
verse 27 or verse 23. Then if any man
say unto you, lo here is Christ or there
believe it not. For as the lightning
cometh out of the east and shineth even
unto the west, so shall the coming of
the son of man be. Let me let me
rephrase that for you all. Jesus said,
"A time is coming where you need to pray
that your fight is not on the Sabbath."
That time is the same time that many are
going to be saying, "Lo, here is Christ.
There is Christ." But I tell you,
believe it not. For as lightning shines
out of the east and comes even unto the
west, so shall the Sabbath. Jesus
prophesied that the Sabbath would be
standing until he comes again. So then
in the Old Testament, God prophesied the
Sabbath is going to be standing for
Gentiles in the New Testament. In the
New Testament, Jesus prophesied the
Sabbath is going to be standing in the
very time that I come back. So make sure
that your flight is not on the Sabbath.
Anyone that comes along and tells you,
"Hey, guess what? You don't need to keep
the law. Guess what? S's been done away
with. Part of the ten commandments is no
longer binding. Then you can know
devil's advocate.
Devil's advocate.
You are arguing the same principle of
the devil. You are arguing that Satan
should have right back into the kingdom.
Because if there is no law, then there
is no wrath. There is no condemnation.
And if there's no condemnation,
everybody gets to go to heaven. It is
not fair to get rid of a law that caused
some people to be lost when the law
stood, but now it's done away with and
those people are still going to be lost.
Shouldn't we commute their sentences?
Either the law stands or it doesn't. You
cannot say, "Well, it doesn't stand for
me, but it stands for them." Either the
law stands or it doesn't. And if it
doesn't, you are arguing without knowing
it that Satan belongs in heaven.
Revelation 22:14, the Bible says,
"Blessed are they that do his
commandments that they may have right to
the tree of life and may enter in
through the gates into the city. For
outside are dogs and sorcerers and
horongers and murderers and idoltors,
and whosoever loveth maketh a lie." In
other words, outside the city are those
who broke the commandments, but inside
the city are those who are there because
they were obedient to God.
They are not saved because they kept the
commandments. They're saved because
Christ covered them with his
righteousness. And he covered them with
his righteousness because they admitted,
"Yes, I've broken all of your law, God,
and I'm going to turn away from breaking
your law. And I know that in turning
away from breaking your law, I'm not
saved now by keeping your law. I am
saved because you covered me. But you
only covered me because I admitted my
nakedness.
The law of God reveals my nakedness. And
if there's any part of the law that I
want to hide or disqualify or say,
"Yeah, that doesn't count. I have I am I
have not fully repented.
Woe unto them, the Bible says, that call
evil good and good evil, that put
darkness for light and light for
darkness, that put bitter for sweet and
sweet for bitter. Woe unto them that are
wise in their own eyes and prudent in
their own sight. Woe unto them that are
mighty to drink wine, wine of Babylon,
y'all, and men of strength to mingle
strong drink, which justify the wicked
for reward, and take away the
righteousness of the righteous from him.
Do you understand this?
When we justify wickedness, when we
justify sin, it is the opposite of
justification by faith. And that's what
so many Christians are doing today. We
are justifying why the law of God is
done away with. We're justifying why the
Sabbath is done away with. And they will
use verses and scriptures. And
Colossians 2:14-16.
Look, all the Sabbaths are done away
with. And the Bible says the law is
nailed to the cross. All of this in
order to justify, in order to argue the
devil's point. And beloved, listen, the
devil quoted scripture. So just because
you quote scripture, doesn't mean you're
quoting it in the way that God meant it.
So you say, you say, "Hey, listen. I
should be saved because I believe." The
problem is you are arguing the devil's
point again. Because notice what James
2:19 says. You believe,
you believe, there is one God. Thou
doest well. The devils also believe and
tremble. But will you not know, oh vain
man, that faith without works is dead?
If you are arguing that just because you
you believe in the God of heaven that
you ought to have right to the kingdom
of heaven and it doesn't matter if you
keep the law then the devil also
believes in that God of heaven and he
also ought to have right to the kingdom
of heaven and he definitely doesn't keep
the law of God. You are arguing you are
being the devil's advocate.
The Bible is clear. Luke 24:27. We got
one more verse after this. Luke 24:27.
The Bible says,
"And that repentance and remission of
sins should be preached in his name
among all nations, beginning at
Jerusalem." This is beautiful. This is
repentance and remission of sin. That's
the gospel right there, y'all.
repentance. Lord, looking at your
commandments, I see that I've broken
every one of them. Every one of them.
I'm not going to make an excuse for not
one of them. I have broken every one of
these commandments. This is genuine
repentance. I've broken them all. And I
will now turn away. I will no longer
practice breaking these commandments. I
may fall, but if I do, I'm going to
repent. I'm going to keep repenting. You
just said that if I repent 70 * 7, you
will forgive me 70* 7. So I know that
all I need to do is repent. But the
devil doesn't want me to repent. The
devil wants me to think you don't need
to repent for that. That law doesn't
even stand. The law in fact is done away
with the whole thing. So some he
convinces that the whole thing is done
away with. Others he convinces that only
part of it is done away with. But it's
all right. The part is done away with.
Don't you don't have to repent for that.
The gospel is repentance from sin, which
is transgression of the law. And when
you genuinely repent, that's all you
need to do. Genuinely be sorry. God
says, "I got you." He covers you. He
says, "I got you."
Because if you're genuinely sorry for
sin, you start doing your best to not do
that sin anymore.
Through the grace and power of the Holy
Spirit, the Holy Spirit begins to work
with you. Man, I don't want to break
these laws anymore. Because in doing
that, I am breaking love. Jesus came to
fix love, not destroy it. And that's
what y'all are saying when you say the
law of God's been done away with. You're
saying love is done away with. And
you're again arguing Satan's point,
y'all, that God is not love.
John 5:32, the Bible says, "I came not
to call the righteous, but sinners to
repentance."
That's it.
You see how simple that is? Why did the
God not come to call the righteous?
Because there is none righteous, know
not one. All of us are guilty of
breaking the law of love.
And so he comes and he says, "Listen,
here's the deal.
You repent and I'll cover you. But if
you don't repent, I can't do anything
for you. Because if I did it for you,
I'd have to do it for Satan, too.
So all I need you to do is repent.
Satan's not repenting. And if you refuse
to repent and you still and and think
you still should have access to heaven
and if you are right then I have to let
Satan in too.
Why would I let you in and not Satan?
I came not to call the righteous but
sinners to repentance. You repent and
I'm going to cover you. You can't be
saved by your own works. You can't be
saved by saying from now on I'm going to
keep the commandments perfectly. If you
kept the commandments perfectly from
this point out, it still wouldn't save
you because you have already sinned. The
only thing that can save you is my
covering you. But the evidence of your
love, the evidence that love has been
fixed in you is that you will keep the
law of love, the Ten Commandments, the
perfect transcript of God's character.
So
my appeal is very simple.
Repent.
Repent and God will cover you.
Repent of every commandment. All the all
10 of them. God summarized them. Love
for God, love for neighbor, it's all the
same thing. It's the law of love. The
Ten Commandments is righteousness
spelled out for dummies. It's love
spelled out for dummies. If you love me,
this is what you will do. If you love
your neighbor, this is what you will not
do.
So God says, "Repent, and I got you."
You're watching this, you're hearing
this for the first time, and you're
realizing, "Whoa, there's stuff I have
not repented for. I thought the law
wasn't was done away with." That's a lie
from the devil. I repent for believing
that. I repent for breaking your law. I
repent for thinking your law no longer
stands. I didn't know I was being the
devil's advocate. And I no longer want
to be the devil's advocate. Because if
God has called me to be a juror, then
I've got to know the difference between
right and wrong. And the only way I can
do that is by trusting God and listening
to his word and abiding by his law.
Because any society that is bent on
lawlessness is a society that is
following the dictates of the lawless
one.
Repent
and be baptized. That was the message of
John the Baptist. That's the message of
Jesus. Very simple. Repent
and I got you.
Repent
and I've got you.
As you're watching this, I it is my
prayer
that if you're hearing this for the
first time,
you will not allow anything to get in
between you
and what God has shown you today.
Help me Lord to repent from breaking
your law and cover me and allow me,
empower me to stop breaking your
commandments, to stop breaking the
Sabbath, to stop believing the lies that
the law of God has been done away with
or altered, changed from the seventh day
of the week to the first day of the
week, done away with all together by the
cross. Help me no longer to believe any
of those lies. Please, Lord, I repent.
Cover me with your grace. Save me by
your grace.
If that's you, I'm going to ask you. You
may be on now or you may be watching
later. Put that one in the chat. You
don't even have to put the one in the
chat, but make that decision in your
mind and follow the truth.
If you're hearing it for the first time
and you're saying, "Okay, I need Bible
study. I need to understand more of
this." that I'm going to ask you. I'm
going to we're going to put a link.
We're going to pin a link in the chat.
Either pin it or put it in the chat. Pin
it at the top. Put it in the chat. If
you want to get in into Bible study to
get greater understanding of these
truths, I'm leading out a Bible study
every Thursday night. It's a baptismal
class. I invite you to join that study
if you are interested in being baptized.
There is the link. There is the uh email
bibleworker living mana.urch. And I'm
going to close in prayer. But before I
do that, let me take you to the last
slide. For those of you who would like
to get a copy of these slides, use your
phone, scan this QR code. It's up on the
screen. And that's how you can get a
copy of the slides. That's how you can
get access to all of our other social
media information. And may God bless
you. May God bless you as you
contemplate the mana that has come from
heaven today. May God bless you. And uh
let's pray. Heavenly Father, thank you
for speaking. Thank you, Lord, for
saving us from being the devil's
advocates,
Lord. We want to be your advocates. We
want to stand for your truth. We want to
stand for your name. We want to stand
for your glory. We want to stand for
your principles, Lord. So, please, for
those who have been the devil's
advocates and did not know it, did not
understand it, were ignorant of it,
ignorant of it, Lord, I pray forgiveness
because you wink in times of ignorance.
Now Lord, now I pray that you would give
them boldness to step out on the truth
and to walk in the truth. Lord, please
empower them to make this decision. I
pray it in Jesus name. Amen. And amen.
May God bless you.